anirudhsethireport.com 2016-11-30

# Privacy Policy - Anirudh Sethi Report

### Our Privacy Policy

This website is administered by Anirudh Sethi Report. We want you to feel secure when visiting our site and are committed to maintaining your privacy when doing so. The following provides an overview of how we protect your privacy during your visit to our site.

### Information we collect

Information on anirudhsethireport.com is gathered when you provide information across various pages on anirudhsethireport.com.

We collect information directly from you in a number of ways, some of which are described in this Privacy Statement. One way is through the use of cookies. Cookies are small files of information which save and retrieve information about your visit to anirudhsethireport.com for example, how you entered our site, how you navigated through the site, and what information was of interest to you.

TIP: If you are uncomfortable regarding cookies use, please keep in mind you can disable cookies on your computer by changing the settings in preferences or options menu in your browser. Disabling cookies may create problems while browsing this site.

We also collect information when you voluntarily submit it to us, when we collect this type of information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for information and how this information will be used. It is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it. We also gather information when you create a user account or register on our site as a subscriber, send us feedback and/or contact us for any assistance.

### How this information helps us?

Anirudh Sethi Report uses your personal information for several general purposes like: to fulfill your requests for certain services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, special offers or other information, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, promote our services, inform you about special offers, or contact you for market research.

### Is your Private Data Safe?

As a commited organization, the data we collect will not be leaked outside our organization in any ways. In the event of a merger, consolidation, collaboration or reorganization involving Anirudh Sethi Report, your personal information will, in most instances, be transferred to the control of the third party that is part of that transaction. So, before you submit any information, we will notify you as to why we are asking for specific information and it is completely up to you whether or not you want to provide it.

### Personal Data

Anirudh Sethi Report is committed to protecting your personal information and do so with certain physical and technological procedures. However, we cannot ensure the security of the information as you transmit it to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. This includes using a secure browser like Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome, Sea Monkey, Netscape or Opera where applicable. **We do not recommend Internet Explorer**.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may amend or change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. We may also, but are not required to, notify you by email or regular mail.

We are interested and commited in maintaining your privacy and creating a valuable resource for you to use. If you have any questions now or during your visit, please contact us.

 **Team Anirudh Sethi Report**
